

CONTACTS

- **L** +375 29 768-80-83
- igors.gudelis@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/igor-gudelis-679855115/
- s igors.gudelis
- igors.gudelis

Citizenship:

the Republic of Lithuania

Employment:

Full time

Relocation possible Ready for business trip

LANGUAGES

English



B2 - Upper Intermediate

Russian



SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- SCSS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Angular 2+
- Angular Material
- RxJS
- Ngrx/Ngxs

IGOR GUDELIS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Minsk, Belarus

Age: 37 years old

WORK EXPERIENCE



03.2020 — Present.

Freelance

Front-End Developer

- Worked in a multilingual team.
- Participated in daily meetings, dev sprint planning, backlog review.
- Implemented designs that work across all modern desktop and mobile browsers.
- Developed features using Serverless on Amazon Web Services.

09.2019 — 03.2020

CactusSoft

Front-End Developer

- Created project's architecture in line with the latest angular development trends.
- Added Redux-based technologies with the ngxs library which helped improve the application maintainability.
- Was responsible for the whole application's lifecycle from start to the deadline.
- Participated in project team meetings and communicated effectively with business analysts, project managers and QA.

12.2018 — 09.2019

VRP Consulting

Front-End Developer

- Created project's architecture in line with the latest angular development trends.
- Integrated Server-side rendering (SSR) with Angular Universal.
- Managed a team of 2 junior engineers.

11.2016 — 12.2018

Ais Novations

Front-End Developer

- Took part in creating the official site of the company.
- Developed individually a well structured, maintainable, easy to understand application frontend while adhering to the defined coding standards.
- Participated in daily meetings, identified and resolved gaps in business requirements.

EDUCATION -



Minsk State Architectural and Construction College

economist

COURSES -



2020

W3Cx, in collaboration with edX.

Front-End Web Developer

https://courses.edx.org/certificates/c8ec0899eede433e9200b7070ad003f2

ABOUT ME -



Front-end Developer with more than four years of experience in developing new software functionalities and updating existing software.

Work experience in a multilingual team and communication with an English-speaking customer.

Demonstrable ability to learn, adapt, share and integrate knowledge across workgroups.

I can work both in a team and independently,

Self-sufficient in the development of assigned tasks, detailoriented, disciplined, motivated.